Guide to the Records of Director of Academic Program Review, Barnett Hamberger 1972-2003 RG 9.7 RG 9.7
New York University Archives
- Series I
  - Middle States Study Abroad, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Middle States/SCE Self Study, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - MSA Self Study Site- Team Visit, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Accreditation, 1992-1993 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Accreditation, 1993-1994 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Accreditation, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Academic Program Review Budget, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058595 5
  - Bagpipe Band Budget, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Registration, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Registration, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - State Education Department Regulations, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - L.J. Oliva, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Commission, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Commission, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Degree Program list, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Blanton-Peale Institute, undated (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Accreditation, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Accreditation, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - State Inventory Programs, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - State Inventory Programs, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - State Ed Department, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - State Ed Department, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - State Ed Department, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - State Attorney General, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Middle States, 1997-1998 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Middle States, 1996-1997 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Middle States- Howard, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - SED Evaluation NYU PhD Programs in Computer Science, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058593 0
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Environmental Health Science Programs, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - SED Site Team Evaluations of Physical Therapy, 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - SED Site Team Visits/Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Psychology Programs (GSAS), 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - SED Site Team Visits/Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Psychology Programs (GSAS), 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Medicine PhD Basic Medicine Program Site Visit Report, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - GSAS Clinical Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - GSAS Community Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - SEHNAP Psychology Development Site Visit Report, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Medicine PhD Environmental Health Science Program Site Visit Report, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - GSAS Experimental Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - GSAS Personnel Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - SEHNAP Psychological Foundations of Reading Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - SEHNAP School Psychology Child School Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1988 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - GSAS Social Personality Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - SEHNAP Special Education Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - GSAS Computer Science Program Site Visit Report, 1990-1991 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - SEHNAP Child/School Psychology Site Visit Report, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - SEHNAP Counseling Psychology Site Visit Report, 1991-1992 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - SEHNAP Counseling Psychology Site Visit Report, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Developmental Psychology, undated (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Athletics Eligibility, 1997-1998 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Athletics, 1997-1998 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Athletics, 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Athletics Academics, 1997-1998 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Athletics EADA ppt, 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Athletic Academics, 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Athletic Academics, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Athletic Academics, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Athletic Rosters--Men, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Athletic Rosters--Men, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Athletic Rosters--Women, 1994-1995 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Athletic Rosters, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - SED PhD Evaluation Child/School Psychology, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04058596 3
  - NYST Doctoral Evaluation-BMS/Dentistry, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - SED Evaluation NYU PhD Programs in Computer Science, 1991-1993 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - SED Evaluation NYU PhD Programs in Computer Science, 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - SED Evaluation NYU PhD Programs in Computer Science, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - SED Doctoral Council, 1994-1995 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - SED PhD Evaluation Counseling Psychology, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - SED Doctoral Evaluations Educational Psychology, 1993 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - SED Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Programs in Education, 1979-1983 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - SED Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Programs in Health and Physical Education, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - SED PhD Evaluation Development Psychology, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - SED Evaluation for NYU Doctoral Programs in Psychology- GSAS/SEHNAP, 1990-1991 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Inventory of Registered Programs, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - SED Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Programs in Psychology- GSAS/SEHNAP, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - SED Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Programs in Psychology- GSAS/SEHNAP, 1988-1989 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - SED Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Programs in School Psychology- GSAS/SEHNAP, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - SED Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Programs in Science Education, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - SED Evaluations of NYU Doctoral Programs in Special Education, 1988-1989 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - General Doctoral Evaluations, 1977-1980 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - General Doctoral Reviews, 1980-1993 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - SED Biological Sciences Review, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - SED Educational Psychology Review SEHNAP, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - SED Occupational Therapy Doctoral Review, 1989-1990 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - SED Health Administration Visit, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - SED Elementary Education MA Review, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - SED Elementary Education MA Review, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - SED Science Education Doctoral Programs Re-Evaluations, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - SED Science Education Doctoral Programs Re-Evaluations, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Basic Medicine Science Programs MED, 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Biological Sciences Program-Dentistry, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Biological Sciences Program- GSAS, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  - GSAS PhD Biological Science Program Site Team Visit Report, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Biological Sciences Program MED, 1982-1984 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluations for NYU Doctoral Biological Sciences Program MED, 1985-1987 (Box 83, Folder 34)
  - SSB Grad, 1996-1997 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  - SED Site Team Visit Evaluation Response for NYU PhD Programs in Environmental Health Sciences and Biological Sciences, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225625 8
  - SED Site Team Evaluations Factual Response for NYU Doctoral Psychology Programs- GSAS/SEHNAP, 1987-1988 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - SED Site Team Evaluations Factual Response for NYU Doctoral Psychology Programs- GSAS/SEHNAP, 1987-1988 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Site Team Visit Responses for NYU Doctoral Psychology Programs- SEHNAP/GSAS, 1987-1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - SED Basic Medical Sciences Reating Committee Reports, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - SED Biological Sciences Rating Committee Reports (Dent, GSAS, MED, Sackler), 1987 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - SED Psychology Rating Com. Rpt, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - SED Psychology Rating Com. Rpt, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - SED Psychology Rating Com. Rpt, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Teachers Education Final Report, 1992-1993 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Background Information for SED Baccalaureate Programs in Teacher Education, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Background Information for SED Site Review of Baccalaureate Programs in Teacher Education, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - SED Reviews of BS Programs in Teacher Education, 1991-1992 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - SEHNAP BA Teacher Education Program Site Visit Report, 1990-1991 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - SED Review of Baccalaureate Programs in Teacher Education, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - SED Review of Baccalaureate Programs in Teacher Education, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - SED PhD Evaluations General, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Background Information on SED Site Review of Baccalaureate Programs in Teacher Education, 1989 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Registration, 1998-1999 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225623 3
  - Registration, 1999-2000 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Middle States Assocation, 1998-1999 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Commission, 1997-1998 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Commission, 1998-1999 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Crapanzano Lawsuit, undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Crapanzano State Ed. Dept, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Crapanzano Middle States Dept., undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Oju Eugene Minima, undated (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Craig James Hearing-Background Information, undated (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Aronson/Charry Case, 1981-1982 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Aronson/Charry Case, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Aronson/Charry Case, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Aronson/Charry Case, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Aronson/Charry Case, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Paul Maxim, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225624 1
  - Athletics Gender Equity, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Coles Development Campaign, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Athletics- Title IX, undated (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Pier 40- Usage, undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Pier 40- Meetings Notes, undated (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Athletics Field Pier 40 General, undated (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Pier 40- Costs, undated (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Pier 40- Agreement, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Fields- Gansevoort, undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Fields- General, undated (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Otote, Moses, undated (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Otote, Moses, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Otote, Moses, undated (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Otote, Moses Osamindinmen, undated (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Otote, Moses, undated (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Otote, Moses, undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Otote, Moses DOB 10-22-53, undated (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Otote, Moses, undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Otote, Moses, undated (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Athletic Fields--Injuries, undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Handbook, undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225621 7
  - Accreditation, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Accreditation, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Accreditation, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Accreditation Chea, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Accreditation List, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - AAU, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1996-1997 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1995-1996 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1994-1995 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Bagpipe Band, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Bagpipe Band Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Bagpipe Band Budget, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Bagpipe Band Scholarship, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Bagpipe Band Scholarship, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Bob Berne, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Canada, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Career Services, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Career Services, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Centers and Institutes, 1997-1998 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - CICU, 1996-1997 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - CHEA, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - CHEA, 1997-1999 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - (New York) SDE PR EDU Humanities (Binder), 1997 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - Occupational Therapy Accreditation, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Report of Institute Self-Study Liason Center: Summary Medical Education, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Report of Institute Self-Study Liason Center: Subcommittee Reports, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - State Postsecondary Review Program Review Process, undated (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - State Ed. Task Force on Outcome, 1999-2000 (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Bagpipe Band, undated (Box 87, Folder 37)
  - (New York) State Ed Program Terminations, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225620 9
  - Graduate Assistants, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Commission, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education Act, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - University Club, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Department of Education, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - University Senate, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - University Senate, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Affairs, 1997-1998 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Trustees, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Torch Club, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Harvey Stedman, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - (New York) State Education Teachers Ed Program, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - State Education Title Changes, 1997 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - State Education Task Force: Sexual Harrassment, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - State Education Regulations, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - State Education New Programs, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - State Inventory of Programs, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - State Ed Doctoral Council, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - State Ed Comments, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - State Ed Comments, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - State Ed Comments, 1998 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - State Education, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - State Education, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - SDE PR SW Social Science, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - SDE PR SSB Social Science, undated (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - SDE PR Social Science, 1998-1999 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - SDE PR Social Science, 1999-2000 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - SED PR GSAS Social Science, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - State Ed Department Terminated Programs, undated (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Licensing, 1998-1999 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225619 1
  - NAICU Task Force, 1998-1999 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - NYU Online, 1998-1999 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Real Estate, 1999-2000 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - State Doctoral Evaluation Periodic Review, 1994-1995 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - State Doctoral Evaluation Periodic Re-Review Psych, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - SDE EDU PR General, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - SDE EDU PR Humanities, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - SDE PR EDU Speech Pathology, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - SDE PRO EDU GSAS Humanities, undated (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - SDE PR GSAS Physical Science, undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - SDE PR EDU Social Science, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - SDE PR GSAS Humanities, undated (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225618 3
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Intercollegiate Athletic Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Academic Honor Roll, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Academic Honor Roll, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Spring Honor Roll, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Honor Roll/Grades, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Academic Honor Roll Spring, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Academic Honor Roll Fall and Honor Letters, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Academics Fall, 1998 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Academics, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Academic Honor Roll Spring, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Athletic Academics, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Academic Office Computerization, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Athletics, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Athletics, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Athletic Academic Team Academic Award, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Athletic Academic Honor Roll Fall, 1999 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Team Academic Award, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Athletic Academic Achievement Awards, 1999-2000 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Athletic Achievement Awards, 1998-1999 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Athletic Academic Achievement Awards, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225633 2
  - Athletic Academic Achievement Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Academic Affairs Office, 1988-1996 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - NCAA Postgraduate Scholarship, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - NCAA, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Athletics Students, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - NCAA, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - NCAA, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - NCAA, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - NCAA Self-Study, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - NCAA Coaches Exam, 1997 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - UAA, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - UAA, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - UAA, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - UAA Delegates, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - UAA Delegates, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - UAA Delegates, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - UAA Delegates, 1996-1997 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - UAA Executive Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - UAA Presidents Council, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Coles, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Coles, 1998-1999 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Coles, 1997-1998 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Letters, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Athletics Recruitment, undated (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Medical Education Database- Section I-IV: Objectives through Education Programs for MD, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225632 4
  - Medical Education Database- Section V-X: Medical Students through Research, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Medical Education Database- Section XI (A):Basic Science Department, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Medical Education Database- Section XI (B): Clinical Science Database, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - SEHNAP Teacher Education Self-Study for the State Education Department: Vol. I General Report, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - SEHNAP Teacher Education Self-Study for the State Education Department: Vol. II Program Report, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - SEHNAP Teacher Education Self-Study for the State Education Department: Vol. III Mathematics Education, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Long Range Plan/Summary Report of Schools and Colleges/Interim Report on University-Wide Planning Commission, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Proposal for Pier40/Athletic Field Files, 1997 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225631 6
  - Social Work Accreditation Volume I/Part I, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Social Work Accreditation Volume I/Part II, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Social Work Accreditation Volume II/Part II, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Social Work Accreditation Volume II/Part II, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Social Work Accreditation Volume III/Appendices, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Survey Report (AMA/AAMC) NYU School of Medicine, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225630 8
  - Evaluation Report/Commission on Dental Accreditation, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Social work Education Accreditation Vol I, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Wagner: Program of Health Policy and Management (ACEHSA) Vol. I, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Wagner: Program of Health Policy and Management (ACEHSA) Vol. II, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Wagner: Program of Health Policy and Management (ACEHSA) Vol. III, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Wagner: Program of Health Policy and Management (ACEHSA) Vol. IV, 1997 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Psychology Accreditation Report Appendices 1-7, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Stern AACSB Self-Study Preconditions, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Stern AACSB Self Evaluations and Peer Review Attachements, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Stern Accounting Accreditation AASCSB Self Evaluation, 1998-1999 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Progress Report- MS in Energetics/Fluid Dynamics/Atmospheric Science, Dept. of Applied Science Self-Study, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Wagner: Statistical Methods for Public, Non-Profit and Health Management, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Assocation: The Liberal Education Program, Vol I, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Wagner: Self Study Urban Planning, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Physical Therapy Application for Interim Accreditation/Evaluation Criteria and Appendices 1-6, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225629 0
  - National League for Nursing (NLN) Self-Study, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Dietetics Self-Study, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Self-Study Dietetic Internship, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Occupational Therapy Appendices IC and ID, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Dance Education NASD Self-Study, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - School of Continuing Education AAS/Physical Therapy Progress Report, 1998 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225628 2
  - Physical Therapy Assistant Program Self-Study On Site, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - NYU Medical School Repiratory Therapy, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Dentistry Self-Study: Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery Part A, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Dentistry Self-Study: Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery Part A and B, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Application for Accreditation Speech Language Pathology, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - GPA Self-Study Report Vol. I, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Health Services Administration, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Wagner: Self-Study Urban Planning, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Journalism Re-Accreditation Report Books, 1, 2, and 3, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225627 4
  - Joint Degree Programs/MS Biomedical Journalism Appendix B- Course Syllabi, 1997-1998 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Social Work Accreditation Vol I, Part I (EVS 1-6), 2002 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Social Work Accreditation Vol I, Part II (Faculty Data Forms), 2002 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Social Work Accreditation Vol II, Part II (BS Program), 2002 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Social Work Accreditation Vol II, Part I (MSW Program), 2002 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Social Work Accreditation Vol II,Appendix A, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Social Work Education Self Study, Volume III Appendices, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Art Therapy Self-study Report to American Art Therapy Assoc., 1997 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225626 6
  - Blueprint for the Millenium, Summary and Committee Reports, Re-Accreditation of School Medicine, 1998-2000 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    3 1142 04225622 5
  - Task Force: Sexual Misconduct, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Torch Club, 2001-2002 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Torch Club Advisory Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Substance Abuse Steering Committee, 1991-1999 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - NYU Online, 1999-2000 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - NYU Online, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Middle States Task Force On Institutional Effectiveness, 1999-2000 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Middle States Task Force On Institutional Effectiveness, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Faculty, 2000-2001 (Box 99, Folder 11)